Finding Aid for the Collection of Pamphlet Maps LSC.0990
UCLA Library Special Collections
Collection of Pamphlet Maps
circa 1750
UCLA Library Special Collections
LSC.0990
17.0 linear feet (32 boxes and 1 oversize folder)
Collection consists of hundreds of pamphlet maps of various places around the world.
Restrictions on Access
Open for research. All requests to access special collections materials must be made in advance using the request button located on this page.
UCLA Catalog Record ID
UCLA Catalog Record ID: 9942328343606533
Scope and Content
Collection consists of hundreds of pamphlet maps of various places around the world.
Online Items Available
Portions of this collection have been digitized and are available online: Pamphlet Maps Collection (7 items).
The same items, plus one additional items, have been digitized and are available online through Calisphere: Pamphlet Maps Collection (8 items).
Maps (documents).
- Pamphlet Maps Collection, 1750-
  General note
  [This is a partial listing of the maps in the collection. Other entries will be made over time.]
  - Bancroft's map of California, Nevada, Utah, and Arizona. San Francisco., 1864; (Colored map, 70 × 85cm. Scale 1:1, 520, 640) (Box 31)
    Ex Libris: Mrs. Grace Somerby
  - Collection of maps. New York: J.H. Colton., 1853-1864 (Box 27)
    Scope and Contents note
    9 maps
    - 1) Colton's Alabama., 1860 (Box 27)
    - 2-3) California. (both have insets of San Francisco)., 1853; 1859 (Box 27)
      - California, 1853; 1 map: col.; 35.5 x 30 cm. on sheet 43.8 x 35.2 cm. folded to 12.5 x 8 cm. tipped into bound cover 12.7 x 8.8 cm (Box 27)
        Includes inset map "City of San Francisco".
        Map of California identified in California Gold Rush Bibliography. Verso of map has population statistics for the counties of California, Census 1952.
        Title from cover of binding: Map of California.
    - 4) Colton's Louisiana.., 1863 (Box 27)
    - 5) J.H. Colton's topographical map of Virginia, Maryland & Eastern Tennesee & part of adjoining states.., 1861 (Box 27)
    - 6) Colton's Virginia.., 1861 (Box 27)
    - 7) Colton's Map of the United States, the Canadas, and.. ..., c.1864 (Box 27)
    - 8) Map of the United States of America, the British Provinces, Mexico, the West Indies and Central America: with part of New Granada, and Venezuela.., 1856 (Box 27)
    - 9) "Colton's Map of the Americas, Africa, and a Portion of the Pacific Oceans" (inset) in Colton's railroad and military map of the United States, Mexico and the West Indies.., c.1864 (Box 27)
  - Faust's pocket map of city and county of San Francisco. Lithographed in colors... 12th edition. San Francisco: H.W. Faust., c.1892; 1 map: col.; 58 x 73 cm. on sheet 65 x 80 cm. folded to 16 x 1 in cover 18 x 10 cm (Box 31)
    Includes inset map "General view of San Francisco Bay"
    On front cover: "Shows blocks numbered, streets, car lines, ward boundaries, parks, squares, cemeteries, wharves, original water front line, half-mile cirtcles from the bay, government reservations, and a general views of the bay and county surrounding the city".
    Relief shown by hachures and spot heights
    1. San Francisco - Description - Maps.
  - The official map of Orange county, California, and adjoining counties, compiled ... by S.H. Finley and J.L. McBride. [Santa Ana]. (c.1923 J.L. McBride)., 1924; 1 map: col.; 50.6 x 51.7 on sheet 54.5 x 55.7 cm. folded to 15 x 9.5 cm. tipped into cardboard portfolio 16.5 x 10.4 cm (Box 31)
    Map compiled from official and private surveys; copyright, December 1923 J.L. McBride of Santa Ana, Cal
  - Map of Virginia City and the Comstock lode, state of Nevada, showing the latest changes up to January 1, 1875. n.p.: Steam print of F. Korbel & brothers., 1 map: col.; 40.7 x 73 cm. on sheet 44.3 x 76 cm. folded to 15.5 x 9.8 cm. and tipped into bound cover 16.5 x 10.8 cm (Box 31)
    1. Nevada - Maps.
    2. Comstock lode, Nevada - Maps.
  - Map of the United States, Canada, Mexico, and the West Indies, with Central America, showing all the routes to California with a table of distances. New York: Thayer, Bridgman & Fanning., 1854; 1 map: col.; 50 x 62 cm. on sheet 55 x 67 cm. folded to 13 x 8 cm. tipped into bound cover 14 x 9 cm (Box 31)
    1. U.S. - Maps.
    2. Mexico - Maps.
    3. West Indies - Maps.
    4. Central America - Maps.
    5. Canada - Maps.
  - Official tranportation and city map of Los Angeles, California and suburbs. Revised car routing showing car lines in official colors of operating companies, with complete route of each line. [Los Angeles., c.1920].; 1 map: col.; 111.5 x 75 cm. on sheet 114.5 x 80.5 cm (Box 31)
    Relief shown by spot heights
    "Copyright 1911 by Laura L. Whitlock for Los Angeles Ry."
    "Los Angeles Railway Company, operating city system. Color of cars and lines map [yellow]"
    "Pacific Electric Raiway Company, routes of interurban system operating to points indicated at margin of map. Color of cars and lines on map [red]"
    "Glendale & Eagle Rock Ry [blue]"
    Mile circles drawn from 12th and Main, center of population.
    Street index included.
  - Bancroft's map of Oregon, Washington, Idaho and British Columbia. San Francisco, 1864.; 1 map: col.; 68 x 82.5 cm. on sheet 79 x 95 cm. folded to 14.5 x 8.8 cm. tipped into bound cover 15.8 x 10.3 cm (Box 31)
    Scale 1:1,520,640.
    Proposed Northern Pacific Railroad route shown.
    Important trails and trade routes shown.
    From the William Starke Rosecrans Papers with ms. annotations in his hand.
- [Card files]
  The following boxes containing oversize maps were missing when the collection was being prepared for relocation from the map room to SRLF: 1, 4, 11, 21, 24, 29, 44.
  - Acosta, Joseph d'
    See Acosta, José de, 1539?-1600.
  - Aa, Pieter van der, America, of nieuw-ontdekte weereld.[1700], 1659-1733.
  - 'T zuider America, van terra firma en Gujana, voor by Rio de la Plata, tot aan de straat Magellaan, en kusten tegen de Zuid-Zee. Leyden, Pieter van der Aa, [1707]; map.; 1. South America - Maps. (Box 35)
    cf. C. Koeman: Atlantes Neerlandici, vol.1 p.5, no.90.
    Ex libris Warren C. Shearman
  - De vooreylanden van America., [1707]; Cf. C. Koeman: Atlantes Neerlandici, vol. 1, p.4 (no.34) (Box 35)
  - De voor-eylanden van America, tagens de vaste Kusten van Florida, Mexico, Nieuw Spanje, Cartagena, Iucatan, en Darien. Met de grenzen aan de Zuyd Zee gelegen. Leide, Pierre van der Aa, [1707]; map.; 1. Caribbean area - Maps. 2. America - Maps. (Box 35)
    Ex libris Warren C. Shearman See next Card
  - Nova delineatio totius orbis terrarum per Petrus van der Aa., 1. World maps. (Box 35)
    Note: Nouveau carté due monde.
    Ex libris Warren C. Shearman.
  - America, of nieuw-ontdekted weereld., [1700]; map.; 1. America-Maps I.Acosta, José d', 1539?-1600. Acosta, Joseph d' (Box 35)
    America, of nieuw-ontdekte weereld, tot de beschryving van Joseph d'Acosta afgebakend. Leyden, Pieter vander Aa [1700]
    Cf. C. Koeman; Atlantes Neerlandici, vol.1, p.5 (no.103)
  - North America. From the French of Mr. D'Anville, improved with the back settlements of Virginia and course of Ohio. Illustrated with geographical and historical remarks. London, Thos. Jefferys, 1755.; Col. map. 46 x 51.5cm.; Mounted on linen, folded into marbled board (Box 30)
    Scale: 1:7,500,00 approx.
  - A map of South America, containing tierra-firma, New Granada, Amazonia, Brazil, Peru, Paraguay, Chaco, Tucuman, Chili and Patagonia. From Mr. d'Anville, with several improvements and additions, and the newest discoveries, London, Robert Sayer, 1787.; map in 2 sheets.; Ex libris Warren C. Shearman (Box 1)
    1. South America - Maps. I. Sayer, Robert, 1725-1794,-publ.
  - Carte générale de l'Allemagne, comprenant F'ensemble des etats de l'Europe centrale. Paris, J.Andriveau-Goujon, 1847.; Col.map.; 1. Germany - Maps. (Box 15)
  - Andrews, Peter
    See the following entry in this catalog: Rocque, Jean, 1704?-1762. A topographical map of the county of Surrey. [1765]
  - A topographical-map, of the county of Kent. by Jn. Andrews, Andrew Dury, & William Herbert. London, Dury and Herbert, ca.1765.; 4 col.map sheets.; I. Gt. Brit. - Maps. (Box 5)
    I. Herbert, William; II. Dury, Andrew
  - Andrews's new map of the West Indies, and part of the coast of South America. London, Andrews and Harris, 1783.; Col.map.; 1. West Indies - Maps; 2. South America - Maps. (Box 5)
  - A new and accurate map of the country twenty-five miles round Windsor. London, Andrews, Faden, 1777.; Col.map; 1.Great Britain - Maps. (Box 5)
  - Tuscia suburbicaria. Roma, 1696.; Map.; 1. Italy - Maps. (Box 1)
    xRomano, Giacomo Filippo Ameti
    MISSING when coll. was prepared for moving form the Map Room to SRLF
  - II Lazio. Roma, 1693.; Map.; 1. Italy - Maps. (Box 1)
    MISSING when coll. was prepared for moving from the MAP room to SRLF.
  - British North America. London, J. Arrowsmith, 1840.; Col.map.; 1. North America - Maps. (Box 6)
  - Outlines of Greece, and adjacent countries; with modern and antient names. London, A. Arrowsmith, 1826.; Col.map in 4 sheets. (Box 26)
  - A new map of Mexico and adjacent provinces compiled from original documents. London, A. Arrowsmith, 1810.; Col.map in 4 sheets. (Box 37)
    1. Mexico - Maps.
    I. Humboldt, Alexander, Freiherr von, 1769-1859
  - Map of Greece and adjacent countries, with ancient and modern names. (Reduced from the one published in six sheets. [London?], 1824.; Col.map; 1. Greece - Maps. (Box 6)
  - A map exhibiting all the new discoveries in the interior parts of North America.II. London, A. Arrowsmith, 1814.; Col.map in 3 sheets; 1. North America - Maps. (Box 36)
    Originally published 1795; additions to June, 1814.
  - Armstrong, W
    See the following entry in this catalog: Armstrong, Andrew; A map of the county of Northumberland. 1769.
  - A map of the county of Northumberland. by Lieut. and W. Armstrong and son. [London?], 1769.; 2 col.map sheets; 1. Gt. Brit. - Maps. (Box 7)
    I. Armstrong, W
  - The county Palatine of Durham, survey'd by Capt. Armstrong and engraved by Thomas Jefferys. [London?], 1768.; Col.map.; 1. Gt. Brit. - Maps. (Box 7)
  - North America., 1755. (Box 30)
    case. Case title: Pocket mirror for North America which exhibits at one view the European settlements with the claims of the English and the French encroachments.
  - A balloon view of London. London, Edward Stanford, 1859.; Pictorial col.map.; 1. London - Maps. (Box 14)
    Cover-title: View of London, shewing the public buildings, parks, palaces, squares, streets, railway stations, &c.
  - Collection of maps. London, ca.1900-1912.; maps.; 1. Gt.Brit. - Maps. (Box 18)
    Bangor; Darlington; Bexhill; Bournemouth; Seaford; Essex; Southampton; Romsey; Essex, Hertford, Middlesex and London; Peterborough; county map of Cambridge; cycling & motoring map of Cambridge district.
  - Bacon, George Washington, 1830-1921.
  - B., M.
    See Bellin, Jacques Nicolas, 1703-1772.
  - America noviter delineate. M. Merian fecit. [Franckfurt am Maijn, M. Merian, 1649]; 1. America - Maps.; map. 36 x 27.8cm. (Box 21)
    Cf. Lowery Collection, p.142.
  - Map of the United states, with its territories; also Mexico and the West Indies. New York, Ensign, Bridgman & Fanning, 1855[c1849]; map. 31½x28½ in. folded to 9½x9 in.; 1. U.S. - Maps. 2. Mexico - Maps. 3. West Indies - Maps. I. Ensign, Bridgman & Fanning. (Box 28)
    In portfolio with title: Map of the United States & Mexico. Scale: 100 miles to an inch.
    "Drawn & engraved by J. N. Atwood, New York." Insets: The world; West Indies; 1850 population of the United States.
  - Quebec, Ontario, New Brunswick, Nova Scotia, Prince Edward Id. & Newfoundland, with the adjacent parts of the United States. London, Edward Stanford, 1879.; Col.map.; 1. North America - Maps; 2. Canada - Maps. (Box 6)
  - Egypt. London, J.Arrowsmith, 1854.; Col.map.; 1. Egypt - Maps. (Box 6)
  - Carte du cours du fleuve de St. Laurent, depuis son embouchure jusqu'au dessus de Quebec. Pour servir à l'histoire générale des voyages. Par M.B. Ing. De la Marine, 1757; map.; 1. Canada - Maps. (Box 35)
    Cf. W. Lowery: The Lowery Collection, 1912, p. 319.
  - Carte de la nouvelle angleterée, nouvelle yorck, et Pensilvanie. Pour à l histoire générale des voyages. Par M.B. Ing. De la mare., [1757]; 1. New England - Maps X. B, M Ex libiris Warren C. Shearman (Box 35)
    Cf. Lowery Collections, 1912, p.319.
    Note: Tom.XIV in 40. no.9; Tome 14 in 80, page 97.
  - Plan of Simla. Calcutta, Surveyer General of India, 1864.; Col.map. (Box 10)
    1. India - Maps.
  - Barnes, R L
    See the folliwng entry in this catalog: A township map of the state of Iowa. 1855.
  - Bancroft's map of Oregon, Washington, Idaho and British Columbia. San Francisco, 1864.; Col. map. 84 x 99cm. (Box 31)
    From the William Starke Roscrans Papers with ms. annotations in his hand.
  - Bancroft's map of California, Nevada, Utah, and Arizona. San Francisco, 1868.; Col. map. 71 x 94cm. (Box 31)
    Scale 1:1,520,640
  - Bancroft's map of California, Nevada, Utah, and Arizona. San Francisco, 1864.; Col. map. 70 x 85cm. (Box 31)
    Ex libris: Mrs. Grace Somerby
  - Bancroft's official guide map of city and county of San Francisco, compiled from official maps in surveyor's office. San Francisco, A. L. Bancroft &co., 1882.; 15x20 in. folded to 7x4 in.; 1. san Francis co - Descr. - Maps. (Box 31)
    In folder with title: Bancrofts map of San Francisco.
    Inset: Skeleton map showing the relative position of San Francisco to the surrounding country.
  - Bancroft's official guide map of city and county of San Francisco, compiled from official maps in Surveyor's Office. San Francisco, 1877.; Col. map. 53 x 75cm. (Box 31)
    Scale 1:23,500.
    Inset: Skeleton map showing relative position of San Francisco to the surrounding country.
    Note: A reference list of prominent places is included, identifying certain important public and commercial establishments.
  - Novo, ed accurato disegno del territorio Cremasco co'suoi confini., n.p., 1741.; Map.; 1. Italy - Maps. (Box 2)
  - Bohn, P D
    See the following entry in this catalog: Faden, William, 1750-l836.; The sea of Marmara or Propontis. London, 1786.
  - Black's road and railway travelling map of Scotland. Edinburgh, A. & c. Black, [ca.l875?]; Col.map; 1. Gt. Brit. - Maps. (Box 6)
    Adam and Charles Black, publishers.
  - Black's road & railway travelling map of England and Wales. [Edinburgh, A. & C. Black, ca.1875?]; 2 copies.; Col.map.; 1. Gt. Brit - Maps (Box 6)
  - Black's military map of upper Italy, from Rome to the Alps, chiefly from Austrian & Sardinian surveys. Edinburgh, Adam and Charles Black., [1859?]; Col.map.; 1. Italy - Maps. (Box 6)
  - Kraljevina Hrvatska u Habsburskoj monarhiji. Sastavio po H. Hanau. Bec., G. Freytag i Berndt, ca.1900.; map.; 1. Yugoslavia - Maps. (Box 24)
  - Bertio, P
    See Bert, Pieter
  - Nova Germaniae Inferioris descriptio, delineate P. Bertio., Ex libris Warren C. Shearman. Taken from an atlas. On verso: Briefve description de la caerte du pays bas. (Box 35)
    1. Europe, Western - Maps. xBertio, P
  - Carte du golphe du Méxique et des isles de 1'Amerique. Pour servir a l'Histoire générale des voyages. Par M. Bellin, Ingr. de la Marine, 1754.; map.; 1. Caribbean area - Maps. (Box 35)
    Cf. Lowery Collection, 1912, p.305.
  - Bradshaw, George, 1801-1853.
    See the following entry in this catalog: Bradshaw's descriptive guide to the Caledonian railway. London, 1848.
  - A new map of Georgia., [1764]; 1. Georgia - Maps.2. Southern states - Maps. (Box 35)
  - A new map of Georgia, with part of Carolina, Florida and Louisiana. collected by Eman: Bowen. [London, 1764]; map. (Box 35)
    In Navigantium atque itinerantiusm bibliotheca, or, a completed Collection of Voyages and Travels, by John Harris. London, 1764. Vol. II, p. 323. Cf. Woodbury Lowery: a descriptive list of maps, 1912, no.491.
  - A map of the British American plantations, extending from Boston in New England to Georgia; including all the back settlements in the respective provinces, as far as the Mississipi [sic]., 1. U.S.-Maps. 2. New England - Maps. 3. Southern states - Maps. (Box 35)
    Above upper margin: Gent.Mag., July, 1754.
    Lower margin: Thos. Bowen sc.
  - An improved map of Wilt Shire.London, Bowels & Thayer, [ca.1760?]; Col.map.; 1. Gt. Brit. - Maps. (Box 6)
  - An accurate map of the county of Sussex. [London?, 1760?]; Col.map.; 1. Gt. Brit. - Maps. (Box 6)
  - An accurate map of Devon Shire. [London?, 1765?]; Col.map; 1. Gt. Brit. - Maps. (Box 6)
  - Stati del serenissimo signor duca de Modena in Italia. [Ferrara?], 1746.; Map.; 1. Italy - Maps. I. Vandelli, Domenico, 1691-1754. (Box 2)
  - Chorografia del ducato di Ferrara. Ferrara, 1758.; Map.; 1. Italy - Maps. (Box 3)
  - Map of the county of Bedford. London, A. Bryant, 1826.; Col.map.; 1. Gt. Brit. - Maps. (Box 9)
  - Nippon [Japan] 1880. Compiled from native maps and the notes of recent travellers. London, Trübner (Box 18)
    Col. map mounted on linen.
    ex libris C. K. Ogden.
  - Bruff, Joseph Goldsborough, 1804-1889.
    See the following entry in this catalog: U.S. Army. Corps of topographical engineers. Florida.
  - Brué Adrien Hubert
    See: Brué Etienne Robert, 1786-1832.
  - Brookes' travelling companion through England and Wales. London, William Darton, 1812.; Col.map.; 1. Gt.Brit. - Maps. (Box 17)
  - L'Amerique divisée., I. Jaillot, Charles Hubert Alexis, 1640-1712.; col.map.; America - Maps. (Box 4)
    L'Amerique divisée en septentrionale et méridionale. revue, corrigée et augmentée par M. Brion de la Tour. Paris, Desnos, 1783.
    On upper margin: Dressée sur les relations les plus recentes Par le Sr. Jaillot. corrigée en 1782.
  - Imperivm Romanum., map.; 1. Europe - Maps. 2. Africa - Maps. (Box 35)
  - Bradshaw's descriptive guide to the Caledonia railway, comprising graphic delineations of all the objects and places along the line; and complete guide to the city of Carlisle.illus. with a map of the line of railway, and adjacent country. London, W.J. Adams, 1848.; 45 p. map; 1. Gt. Brit. - Maps; (Box 22)
    I. Bradshaw, George, 1801-1853.
  - Pianta topografica di Roma antica, con i principali monvmenti. [Rome?], 1850.; Map.; 1. Italy - Maps. (Box 13)
    Similar in execution to Pianta topografica.
  - Calvo, Rafael Maria
    See the following entry in this catalog: Garcia Conde, Diego Plano general de la ciudad de Mexico. 1830.
  - Vue des glaces au milieu desquelles., 1. Russia - Maps. (Box 35)
    idées qu'on s'est formé du Kamchatka et de ses environs.
    Note on upper r-h margin: IVe carte relative Au Mem. lu a l'Academie le 9 Aout 1752.
    Ex. libris Warren C. shearman
  - A new map of the terraqueous globe according to the ancient discoveries and mos general d divisions of it into continents and oceans. Delin. M. Burghers sculpt. Univ.Oxon., map.; 1. World maps. (Box 35)
    "Dedicated to his highness William, Duke of Gloucester.
  - Vue des glaces au milieu desquelles l'on voit la peche qui se fait au nord-est de l' asie. Extraite d'apres la Carte de LoEmpire russien en langue Russe par Philippe Buache. [Paris] Publiée sous le Privilege de l'acad. des Sciences du 7 Juillet, 1753.; col.map. (Box 35)
    Left hand of map: Réduction d'une carte publiéeà Nuremberg, representant l'une des premieres
  - Carte de géometrique des découvertes de l'amiral de Fonte er de son capitaine Bernarda comparée avec le systeme de la carte Angloise publiée par l'ecrivain du vaisseau la Californie. Paris, sur le Quay de l'Horloge, 1752.; map.; 1. America - Maps. (Box 35)
    Cf. Lowery Collection, p.300.
    Ex libris warren C. Shearman
  - Carte des terres aux environs du Japon., 1. Japan - Maps. 2. Arctic regions - Maps. (Box 35)
    I. Kaempfer II. Sloane, SinsHans, 1660-1753.
  - Carte des terres aux environs du Japon Ou du nord-est de l'Asie et du nord-ouest de l'Amerique extradite d'une carte japonnoise de l'universe apportée en Europe par Kaempfer et déposé dans le Cabinet de feu Mr. Hans-Sloane. [Paris] Academie des Sciences, [1753]; col.map. (Box 35)
    Note: Vie carte rélative au Mem. Lu à l'acad.
    Le 9 Aout 1752.
  - Buache, Jean Nicholas, 1741-1825.
  - Cary's new and accurate plan of London and Westminster, the borough of Southwark and parts adjacent. London, printed for Jno. Cary, 1824.; Col.map.; 1. London - Maps. (Box 7)
  - Carte generale de l'empire de Russie. n.p., 1787.; Map.; 1. Russia - Maps. (Box 2)
  - Carte de l'archipel et isles de l'archipel. Na de stellinge en ondervinding der hedendaegsche stuur luyden., [ca.1670?]; map.; 1. Mediterranean area - Maps. (Box 35)
  - Carte de la Grece moderne. n.p., [1765?]; map.; 1. Greece - Maps (Box 1)
  - Carte de la Grece ancienne. n.p., [ca. 1765]; map.; 1. Greece - Maps. (Box 1)
  - Carta generale dell'America con porzione della Polinesia o parte orientale dell' Oceanica, secondo le nuove scoperte ed osservazioni. Roma, Presso la Calcografia Camarale, [ca.1800?]; map in 9 sheets; 1. U.S. - Maps. 2. Islands of the Pacific - Map (Box 35)
  - Carta corografica delle provincie di Cuneo e di Porto Maurizio. Riveduta nell' anno 1874. Torino e Firenze, Gio. Batt. Maggi, map.; 1. Italy - Maps. (Box 13)
  - Carta amministrativa del regno d'Italia co'suoi stabilimenti. per ordine del ministro della Guerra, e marina. Also: carta delle provincie Illiriche, 1813.; 2 maps.; 1. Italy - Maps. (Box 23)
  - Cano y Olmedilla, Juan de la Cruz
    See: Cruz Cano y Olmedilla, Juan de la, 1734-1790.
  - Caylus, Comes de
    See the following entry in this catalog: Anne Claude Philippe, comte des, 1692-1765, literatura.
  - The catholic Netherlands, divided into their several provinces, with the roads. London, Robert Sayer, 1772.; Col. map; 1. Netherlands,- Maps; I. Sayer, Robert, 1725-1794, publ. (Box 8)
  - Cassini, Jacques, 1677-1756.
  - Cassini, Jacques Dominique
    See: Cassini, Giovanni Domenico, 1625-1712.
  - The Cassini world map of 1696, from the original in the William L. Clements library, University of Michigan. [Ann Arbor? Mich., 1940?]; Diameter; 55m., on leaf: 66 x 61 ½cm. folded to 33 x 22cm.; 1. Maps, Early. I. Michigan. University. William L. Clements library. II. Title: World map of 1696. xCassini, Jacques Dominique (Box 9)
    Collotype facsimile of Cassini's Planisphere terrestre of 1696.
  - Cary's reduction of his large map of England and Wales, with part of Scotland. London, J.Cary, 1816.; Col.map.; 1. Gt, Brit. - Maps. (Box 7)
    ".1796 and corrected to the year 1816." (cop.1)
    ". corrected to the year 1830" (cop.2)
  - A new map of the principality of wales, divided into counties. London, Cary, 1818.; Col.map.; 1. Gt. Brit. - Maps. (Box 7)
  - Cary's new map of England and Wales, with part of Scotland. 2d ed. London, J. Cary, 1816.; 3 col.map sheets; 1. Gt. Brit. - Maps. (Box 7)
  - A new map of Derbyshire, divided into hundreds. London, J. Cary, 1816.; Col.map.; 1. Gt. Brit. - Maps (Box 7)
  - Diocesi Padovana con tutta la sua estensions ne vicini territorr. Padova, 1720.; Col.map.; 1. Italy - Maps. (Box 3)
  - Topografia geometrica dell' agro Romano. Intagliata da Pietro Paolo Girelli Romano. Roma, Domenico de Rossi, 1704.; map.; 1. Italy- Maps. (Box 2)
    xGirelli, Pietro Paolo
  - Carta topografico. del Bolognese. e di parte del Ferrarese. Andrea Chiesa periot per parte di Bologna. Giamba. Migliaria perito per parte di Ferrara ho fatto il confronto della presente carta congl. originali., l762.; map.; 1. Italy - Maps (Box 2)
    1. Migliaria, Giambattista
  - Carte du Paraguai, du Chili, du Detroit de Magellan &c., [1719]; map.; 1. South America - Maps. (Box 35)
    Tom. VI, no.33, pag.135. [Chatelain: Atlas historique, 1705-1720. Cf. Lowery, p.224